Guide to the Art Poster File ca. 1890-1910 PR55-1
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
Art Poster File
Bulk, 1895-1896
1890-1910
PR55-1
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
0.42 Linear feet
The Art Posters include advertisements for books, magazines, and newspapers
Organization of the Collection
This collection is organized into the following three series:
Series I: Magazine and Journal Posters
Series II: Book Posters
Series III: Newspaper Posters
Historical Note
The Art Posters include colorful advertisements for books, magazines and newspapers. They were produced during a brief American art poster craze, launched in the 1890s when New York publishers hired illustrators Aubrey Beardsley, Elisha Brown Bird, William H. Bradley, George Reiter Brill, William L. Carqueville, George Wharton Edwards, Charles Dana Gibson, Archie Gunn, Ernest Haskell, Edward Penfield, Nelly Umbstaetter, Henry Sumner Watson, Charles Hubbard Wright, and others to create striking graphic advertising posters to sell their monthly magazines. The bold, clever images, inspired by French art styles and the Arts and Crafts movement, became so collectible that publishers switched to monthly pictorial covers.
Scope and Contents Note
The Art Posters File consists of approximately 612 striking prints used to advertise magazines, books, and newspapers. Notable artists include Edward Penfied and Joseph J. Gould. Art Posters make up Series I of a larger Poster File (PR 055) held by the Department of Prints, Photographs and Architectural Collections.
Provenance
The posters come from a variety of donors.
Access Restrictions
Available by advance appointment only. To schedule an appointment, contact the Print Room Librarian at printroom@nyhistory.org. Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.)
Related Material at the Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections
Art posters from this same time period can also be found in the Bella C. Landauer Collection of Advertising and Business Ephemera (PR 031). Other posters can be found in the Poster File (PR 055).
Atlantic Monthly Press, publisher; Bachelor of Arts, publisher; Baker & Godwin, printer; Beardsley, Aubrey, 1872-1898, artist.; Bearings, publisher; Bird, Elisha Brown, 1867-1943, artist; Black cat; Bradley, Will, 1868-1962, artist.; Brill, George Reiter, artist; Carqueville, William L., 1871-1946, artist; Century Company, publisher; Century magazine; Chambers, Robert W. (Robert William), 1865-1933, artist; Charles Scribner's Sons, publisher; Cosmopolitan, publisher; Cox, Charles A., artist; Dixon, Maynard, 1875-1946, artist; Dow, Arthur W. (Arthur Wesley), 1857-1922, artist; Edwards, George Wharton, 1859-1950, artist; Flagg, James Montgomery, 1877-1960, artist; Gibson, Charles Dana, 1867-1944, artist; Godey's magazine; Gould, Joseph J., artist; Gunn, Archie, b. 1863, artist; Harper & Brothers, publisher; Harper's magazine; Haskell, Ernest, 1876-1925, artist; Hazenplug, Frank, 1874-1931, artist; Henslow, W. W. (William Wallace), 1856-1915, artist; Illustrated American; J.B. Lippincott Company, publisher; Kendall, William Sergeant, 1869-1938, artist; Leyendecker, J. C., 1874-1951, artist; Lippincott's magazine; McClure's magazine; McManus, Blanche, b. 1869, artist; Murphy, Nelly Littlehale, artist; New York herald tribune; New York Sunday journal; New York times; New York world (New York, N.Y.: 1861); Outing (1885); Parrish, Maxfield, 1870-1966, artist; Penfield, Edward, 1866-1925, artist; Peterson magazine; Philadelphia press (Philadelphia, Pa.: 1880); Prang's chromo; Recreation; Reed, Ethel, artist; Rhead, Louis, 1857-1926, artist; Scotson-Clark, G. F. (George Frederick), 1872-1927, artist; Scribner's magazine; St. Nicholas (New York, N.Y.); The Bookman, publisher; The Chap-book; The Echo, publisher; The Sun; To Date; Vanity fair (New York, N.Y.); Watson, Henry Sumner, 1868-1933, artist; Wright, Charles Hubbard, artist; Young ladies' journal (American ed.); Advertising -- Books -- Posters; Advertising -- Periodicals -- Posters; Book & magazine posters -- 19th century; Lithographs; Prints
- Series I: Magazine and Journal Posters, 1
  Scope and Contents Note
  Series I, Magazine and Journal Posters, contains 378 posters that date from 1890 to 1910.
  Posters are arranged alphabetically by journal and then chronologically. Each poster has been assigned an item number based on this arrangement. Posters are housed in flat files by item number.
  Artists, where identified, are listed in parentheses after the magazine title.
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ Vacation Number/ Town and Gown Rown at Princeton (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1895/07/00-1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0001)
  - The Bachelor of Arts for October/ An American Athlete in England (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0002)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ Christmas Number (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0003)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ February/ Reduced to 25 cents (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0004)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ The Monroe Doctrine by Theodore Roosevelt (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0005)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ Eastern Number (Rogers, A. P.), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0006)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ John C. Ropes replies to Theodore Roosevelt on the Monroe Doctrine (Rogers, A. P.), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0007)
  - The Bachelor of Arts (Rogers, A. P.), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0008)
  - The Bachelor of Arts for June (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0009)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ Princeton 1746-1896 (Watson, Henry Sumner [1868-1933]), 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0010)
  - The Bachelor of Arts/ November, 1895/11/00ca? (Item PR-055-001-0011)
  - Bearings/ Decoration Day Cycle Races (Cox, Charles A.), 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0012)
  - Bearings/ Out Today (Cox, Charles A.), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0013)
  - Bearings/ For Sale Here (Cox, Charles A.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0014)
  - Bearings/ 10 cents/ For Sale Here (Cox, Charles A.), 1895/00/00-1896/00/00? (Item PR-055-001-0015)
  - Bearings/ Out Today (Cox, Charles A.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0016)
  - Bearings/ The Cycling Authority of America/ Out Today/ For Sale Here (Cox, Charles A.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0017)
  - Bearings/ The Cycling Authority of America/ Out Today/ For Sale Here (Cox, Charles A.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0018)
  - Bearings/ Out Today/ For Sale Here (Cox, Charles A.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0019)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0020)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0021)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale (attributed)), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0022)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale (attributed)), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0023)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0024)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0025)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0026)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0027)
  - The Black Cat (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0028)
  - The Black Cat/ Trade Mark/ For Sale Here (Umbstaetter, Nelly Littlehale (attributed)), 1896/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0029)
  - The Bookman/ A Literary Journal/ vol. 1 no. 1/ "I am a Bookman" James Russell Lowell (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0030)
  - The Bookman/ April (Flagg, James Montgomery), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0031)
  - The Bookman/ A Literary Journal/ May Number (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick [1873-?]), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0032)
  - The Bookman/ A Literary Journal/ July Number (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick [1873-?]), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0033)
  - The Bookman/ Drumsheugh's Love Story, 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0034)
  - The Bookman/ Xmas Number (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0035)
  - The Bookman for November (Christy, Howard Chandler), 1896/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0036)
  - The Bookman /Christmas Number (Rhead, Louis John (1857-1926)), 1896/12/00? (Item PR-055-001-0037)
  - The October Bookman (Parker, G. Cushman), 1901/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0038)
    Oversize Folder
    This item is housed in Oversize Folder 53
  - The June Bookman (Parker, G. Cushman), 1902/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0039)
  - The Bookman/ A Literary Journal (Flagg, James Montgomery), 0000/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0040)
  - The Bookman/ March (Norton, Melanie Elisabeth? (attributed)), 0000/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0041)
  - The Bookman (Norton, Melanie Elisabeth), 0000/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0042)
  - The Bookman/ Sep., 0000/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0043)
  - The Bookman/ "The Busy Man's Literary Journal" (Edwards, George Wharton), 0000/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0044)
  - The Bookman/ For Sale Here/ Price, 20 cents, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0045)
  - June Century/ The Matterhorn/ Play and Work, 1891/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0046)
  - A New Life of Napoleon magnificently illustrated/is now beginning in/The Century Magazine/ The Sun of Austerlitz (Grasset, Eugene/ Drake, Will H.?), 1894/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0047)
  - A New Life of Napoleon magnificently illustrated/is now beginning in/The Century Magazine/ The Sun of Austerlitz (Grasset, Eugene/ Drake, Will H.), 1894/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0048)
  - The January Century (Metivet, Lucien), 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0049)
  - The Century/ February Midwinter Number/ Napoleon At Toulon (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0050)
  - The Century for March/ contains The Marriage of Napoleon/ Illustrated articles on Hermann Con Hermholtz and Eugene Ysaye (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0051)
  - The Century for March - Marriage of Napoleon (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0052)
  - The Century for April/ Contains Napoleon's Campaign in Italy/ Recent Inventions of Nikola Tesla (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0053)
  - The Century for April/ Contains Napoleon's Campaign in Italy/ Recent Inventions of Nikola Tesla (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0054)
  - The Century/ Brilliant Chapters in the Napoleon Life/ "The Princess Sonia" by Julia Magruder Illustrated by Charles Dana Gibson (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0055)
  - The Century/ Brilliant Chapters in the Napoleon Life/ "The Princess Sonia" by Julia Magruder Illustrated by Charles Dana Gibson (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0056)
  - The June Century/ Napoleon in Egypt (Grasset, Eugene), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0057)
  - The July Century (Woodbury, Charles H.), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0058)
  - The Century/ Midsummer Holiday Number (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0059)
  - The Century/ Midsummer Holiday Number (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0060)
  - The Century for September/ Contains Articles on the Tuileries "Aquatic Gardening," "Hunting Among the Omahas". (Edwards, George Wharton), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0061)
  - October Century (Lawrence, Herbert Myron [1852-1937]), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0062)
  - The Century for Xmas/ containing a selection of twelve reproductions of the wonderful paintings by Tissot illustrating The Life of Christ (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1895/12/00? (Item PR-055-001-0063)
  - The Century for Xmas (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0064)
  - January Century/ New Year's Number/ A Midsummer Midnight in the Antarctic, 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0065)
  - January Century/ New Year's Number/ A Midsummer Midnight in the Antarctic, 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0066)
  - Midwinter February Century/ The Story of the Development of Africa by Henry M. Stanley (Lawrence, Herbert Myron [1852-1937]), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0067)
  - The Century for March/ The Elder Dumas/ John Randolph of Roanoke (Bird, Elisha Brown [1867-1943]), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0068)
  - The Century for March/ The Elder Dumas/ John Randolph of Roanoke (Bird, Elisha Brown [1867-1943]), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0069)
  - The April Century/ Four Lincoln Conspiracies/ 100,000 Reward from article by Victor Louis Mason of War Department, 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0070)
  - May Century/ Crowning of a Czar (De Yongh), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0071)
  - The Century Magazine for June (Rhead, Louis John [1857-1926]), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0072)
  - The Century/ The July Number (Potthast, Edward), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0073)
  - The Century/ Midsummer Holiday Number/ First Prize Century Poster Contest/ Elihu Vedoer/ F. Hopkinson Smith/ Henry J. Hardenbergh/ Judges (Leyendecker, Joseph Christian [1874-1951]), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0074)
  - The Century for September (Rosenberg, Henry Mortika), 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0075)
  - The Century for October/ Charming Pictures of Child Life in France/ Napoleon at St. Helena, 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0076)
  - The Century for November/ "Campaigning with Grant"/ "Hugh Wynne, Free Quaker"/ Opening Chapters of the New Serials (Hambidge, Jay), 1896/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0077)
  - The Christmas Century/ Campaigning with Grant/ Campaigning with Washington/ "Hugh Wyne Free Quaker" (Hambidge, Jay), 1896/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0078)
  - The Christmas Century/ Campaigning with Grant (Hambidge, Jay), 1896/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0079)
  - January Century/ Hail to the Chief/ Grant in the Wilderness Campaign, 1897/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0080)
  - The Century for February/ Campaigning with Grant/ Dr. Weir Mitchell's Novel of the Revolution "Hugh Wynne Free Quaker", 1897/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0081)
  - Century July/ Big Game/ Sports in the 17th Century (Drake, Will H.), 1897/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0082)
  - The Century/ Midsummer Holiday Number/ August/ Second Prize Century Poster Contest (Parrish, Maxfield), 1897/08/00 (Copyright 1897) (Item PR-055-001-0083)
  - The Century/ Second Prize Poster Contest (Parrish, Maxfield), 1897/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0084)
  - The October Century/ The Heroism of the New York Police by Theodore Roosevelt (Hambidge, Jay), 1897/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0085)
  - The May Century/ The Story of the Captains/ Personal Narratives of the Battle off Santiago/ By Officers of the American Fleet (Edwards, Edward), 1898/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0086)
  - The Christmas Century/ Lieutenant Hobson's Story of the Sinking of the "Merrimac", 1898/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0087)
  - January Century/ The Sinking of the Merrimac, 1899/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0088)
  - The November Century/ Begins Capt. Sigbee's Own Story of the Destruction of the "Maine"/ Sold Here, 1899/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0089)
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine/ Christmas Number/ vol. LIX, no. 2, 1899/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0090)
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine/ New Year's/ vol. LIX no. 3 (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)?), 1900/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0091)
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine vol. LIX, no. 3 (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1900/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0092)
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine vol. LIX, no. 3 (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1900/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0093)
  - The Century for November/ A Year of American Humor (Edwards, George Wharton), 1901/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0094)
  - The Chap-Book/ The Blue Lady (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1894/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0095)
  - The Chap-Book (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0096)
  - The Chap-Book/ Pegasus (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0097)
  - The Chap-Book/ Thanksgiving No. (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0098)
  - The Chap-Book (Bragdon, Claude F.), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0099)
  - The Chap-Book/ "Pan" (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1895/07/00-1895/08/00? (Item PR-055-001-0100)
  - The Chap Book/ The Clowns (Bird, Elisha Brown (1867-1943)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0101)
  - The Chap Book/ Being a Miscellany of Curious and Interesting Songs, Ballads, Tales, Histories, and ?" (Bragdon, Claude F.), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0102)
  - The Chap Book (The Black Lady) (Hazenplug, Frank (1873-after 1911)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0103)
  - The Chap Book "The Green Lady" (Hazenplug, Frank (1873-after 1911)), 1896/06/01 (Item PR-055-001-0104)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ Price 15 cents/ Paolo and Francesca. But "Ouida", 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0105)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ What China Should Do by General Lord Worsely (Marold, L.), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0106)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ An Illustrated Monthly Magazine/ Ocean Bathing on French Coasts/ The Paris Salons of '95, 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0107)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ An Indian Story, by Rudyard Kipling (etc.)/ The Myth of "The 400" by Mrs. Burton Harrison/ July Now Ready/ Price 10 cents, 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0108)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ Bicycling for Women (Rockwood, N. Y. (photographs for The Cosmopolitan)), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0109)
  - The Cosmopolitan/ The Last of the Jungle Stories, by Rudyard Kipling/ Price 10 cents (Drake, Will H./ Cabrinety), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0110)
  - A Great Holiday Number--The Cosmopolitan/ Original Illustrations by L. Rossi, Dan Beard, Eric Pape, F. O. Small, R. C. W. Bunny, G. H. Boughton, A. R. A. (Rossi, Lucius), 0000/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0111)
  - Harper's April (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0112)
  - Harper's July (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0113)
  - Harper's August/ Bathing Suits (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0114)
  - Harper's September (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0115)
  - Harper's November/ Football Yale vs. Harvard (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0116)
  - Harper's Christmas (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1894/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0117)
  - Harper's January (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0118)
  - Harper's/ February/ To My Valentine (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0119)
  - Harper's March (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0120)
  - April Harper's/ Joan of Arc (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0121)
  - Harper's May (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0122)
  - Harper's June (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0123)
  - Harper's/ The German Struggle for Liberty (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0124)
  - Harper's August (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0125)
  - Harper's September/ Three Gringos In Central America/ Metal Telegraphy Again--Mark Twain (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0126)
  - Harper's September/ Three Gringos In Central America/ Metal Telegraphy Again--Mark Twain (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0127)
  - Harper's October (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0128)
  - Harper's November (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0129)
  - Harper's November (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0130)
  - Harper's Christmas (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0131)
    This item is housed in Oversize Folder 52
  - Harper's Christmas (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0132)
    This image should be housed in Oversize Folder 52, but is missing.
  - Harper's January/ In Washington's Day/ by Woodrow Wilson/ Illustrated by Howard Pyle (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0133)
  - Harper's January (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0134)
  - Harper's January (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0135)
  - Harper's February (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0136)
  - Harper's March (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0137)
  - Harper's March (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0138)
  - Harper's April (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0139)
  - Harper's April (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0140)
  - Harper's April (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0141)
  - Harper's May (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0142)
  - Harper's May (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0143)
  - Harper's June (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0144)
  - Harper's June (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0145)
  - Harper's July (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0146)
  - Harper's August/ Tom Sawyer Detective/ A New Story by Mark Twain begins in this number (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0147)
  - Harper's August/ Tom Sawyer Detective/ A New Story by Mark Twain begins in this number (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0148)
  - Harper's September (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0149)
  - Harper's September (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0150)
  - Harper's October (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0151)
  - Harper's October (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0152)
  - Harper's Christmas (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0153)
  - Harper's Magazine/ On Snow Shoes to the Barren Grounds (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0154)
  - Harper's Magazine/ On Snow Shoes to the Barren Grounds (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0155)
  - Harper's February (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1897/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0156)
  - Harper's February (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1897/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0157)
  - Harper's November (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1897/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0158)
  - Stirring Times in Austria Described by Mark Twain/ In Harper's March, 1898/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0159)
  - Lippincott's/ Mrs. Hallam's Companion (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1894/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0160)
  - Lippincott's/ The Waifs of Fighting Rocks (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0161)
  - Lippincott's/ The Chapel of Ease (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0162)
  - Lippincott's/ A Tame Surrender (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0163)
  - Lippincott's/ Alain of Halfdene (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0164)
  - Lippincott's April/ Alain of Halfdene (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0165)
  - Lippincott's/ The Lady of Las Cruces (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0166)
  - Lippincott's/ The Lady of Las Cruces (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0167)
  - Lippincott's/ The Battle of Salamanca (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0168)
  - Lippincott's/ A Social Highwayman (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0169)
  - Lippincott's/ Little Lady Lee (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0170)
  - Lippincott's/ A Case in Equity (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0171)